<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="first_attraction_string">Mt. kitanglad is an active volcano. Located in the Kitanglad Mountain Range in Bukidnon province of Mindanao island. It is the fourth highest mountain in the Philippines and has an approximate height of 2,899 meters.</string>
    <string name="first_attraction_title">MOUNT KITANGLAD</string>
    <string name="first_attraction_second_string">The name \'KITANGLAD\' was derived from a legend that there was once a great flood that submerged the native lands of Bukidnon and only the tip of the mountain, the size of a \'Tanglad\'(Lemon Grass), remained visible (\'Kita\' in Visayan). It is considered as an ancestral domain of several old cultural communities like the Bukidnons, Higaonons and Talaandigs. In 2009, Mount Kitanglad Range Natural Park(MKRNP) was declared as an ASEAN Heritage Park.</string>
    <string name="second_attraction_title">DAHILAYAN FOREST PARK</string>
    <string name="second_attraction_string">A tourist destination that offers an array of fun activities for the whole family, and for all ages. Asia’s Longest Dual Zipline, Skytower Base Jump ride 8 storey platform this is the highest parajump in the Philippines using a cell site tower. Riders experience a split second free fall followed by a gradual descent , ending in a soft landing in less than 10 seconds. and many more..</string>
    <string name="second_attraction_second_string"><![CDATA[Since its opening in September 2009, Zipzone has been visited to over a thousand enthusiasts, including a courageous 2 year old and a 77 year old grandpa. Located at Barangay Dahilayan, Manolo Fortich Bukidnon, Dahilayan Forest Park is nestled at the foot of Mount Kitanglad 4,700 ft. above sea level.]]></string>
    <string name="third_attraction_title">BLUE WATER CAVE</string>
    <string name="third_attraction_string">The “Blue Water Cave” is a natural tourist attraction hidden in the lush valley of a river that flows underground in the connecting caverns of the San Jose village. It is located in the Village of San Jose right after a high bridge that marks the boundary of Quezon and Maramag. The trail to the blue waters will lead you to an enormous white rock cliff where rock wall climbers enjoy pulling themselves up to a steep rock surrounded by amazing rock formations. You can reach the blue water cave down to a narrow trail to reach the riverbank of Pulangi River.</string>
    <string name="third_attraction_second_string">The cave is enchanting and blue waters is magnificent. You can actually swim and be at one with nature. Bright and turquoise waters that would truly refresh you from a day’s walk – this is definitely a one of a kind adventure that would truly be on top of your bucket list.</string>
    <string name="fourth_attraction_title">SUMALSAG CAVE</string>
    <string name="fourth_attraction_string"><![CDATA[History dictates that Sumalsag Cave belongs to the Municipality of Manolo Fortich. A place of excitement for the cavers and spelunkers, Sumalsag Cave is the longest cave in Northern Bukidnon with approximately 1,859 meters from the entrance to its distinct exit where one has to dive underwater to see the outside world after hours of murky and exciting adventure inside the cave.]]></string>
    <string name="fourth_attraction_second_string">The height of the cave varies from one meter to 20 meters and its width varies from less than a meter to a more spacious 9 meters and boasts of its abundance of stalactites and stalagmites. If you’re into an extraordinary adventure, be ready to slide, crawl, swim or even wriggle your body as you move about inside this magnificent Sumalsag Cave.</string>
    <string name="main_attraction_title">THE PROVINCE OF BUKIDNON</string>
    <string name="main_attraction_string">The name \'Bukidnon\' means \'Highlander\' or \'Mountain Dweller\'. It is well endowed with natural scenic spots. Its a vast land area possesses diverse tourist spots, both natural and manmade. Bukidnon is best visited not only during summer season but all year round. Whether you are an outdoorsy person or just a mere vacationist. Its a landlocked province in the philippines located in the Northern Mindanao region.</string>
    <string name="main_attraction_second_string">The province is considered to be the food basket of Mindanao, being the major producer of rice and corn in the region. Products from plantations in the province also include pineapples,bananas and sugarcane. It is known as the watershed of Mindanao.It is endowed with six major river systems namely: Pulangi, Tagoloan, Cagayan, Manupali, Muleta and Bobonawan Rivers These rivers carved the landscape of the province creating numerous canyons. The province is inhabited by 1,415,226 residents.</string>


</resources>
